Konrad Strachan

web3 CTO / Lead Developer

konrad.strachan@gmail.com
 linkedin.com/in/konradstrachan

Øgithub

ß London, UK



SUMMARY

Konrad has been a technologist and developer since he received his first PC at 7 years old and, impatient for software to load, he started reading the thick developer reference and embarked on his journey of building. He is a deeply curious and passionate technologist who enjoys being hands on researching and building as much as he loves supporting and mentoring others to grow.

Comfortable both being internally focused supporting and reinforcing growth from within and equally as passionate to externally represent and communicate about the projects he's involved in.

SELECTED EXPERIENCE

Rhino.fi (previously DeversiFi)

Chief Technology Officer

Aug 2020 - Aug 2023

Grew technology function and business from initial founding team to 30 person startup with mature delivery pipelines $\,$

Responsible for setting technology vision and mentoring teams to support execution

Transformed organisation to be strongly product and end-user centric focusing on user outcomes and business north star metrics

Lead Developer

May 2020 - Jul 2022

Designed and built high performance matching engine for SPOT in-house market execution which by 2023 had handled > \$1.5 Billion USD in volume without issue

Designed and built first Layer 2 AMM engine allowing for gas free interactions with truly trustless pools of user supplied liquidity

CryptoCompare (now known as CCData)

Head of Data

Jul 2018 - May 2020

Hired, built and managed team of developers and QA as well as introduced development best practices and improved safety throughout all dev teams

Performed project manager and business analyst roles providing interface between the Business and external customers and development teams

Implemented incident response policies and multi-tier support processes

Senior Software Developer

Nov 2017 - May 2020

Architected and built low latency market data infrastructure for contribution and collection plus processing of trade and orderbook data $\frac{1}{2} \int_{-\infty}^{\infty} \frac{1}{2} \left(\frac{1}{2} \int_{-\infty}^{$

Architected and built fault tolerant data contributions platform to Thomson Reuters (Refinitiv) using Elekton APIs

TeamViewer

Senior Software Developer

Oct 2014 - Nov 2017

Worked on the TeamViewer Windows desktop client and heavily involved in Windows service development for ITbrain platform for AntiMalware and System Monitoring

Implemented system and low level hardware monitoring for ITbrain Monitoring

Ionising Software

Game Developer

Aug 2012 - Sep 2014

Designed and developed game engine, framework and libraries as well as software licensing system (client and server side) alongside Security auditing

Thomson Reuters (now known as Refinitiv)

Software Developer

Aug 2008 - Jun 2012

Involved in development of financial middleware software ConteX4/5 used for routing market and trade information at top institutions around the world

Contributed to development of core Reuters Market Data Systems (CSG CCG)

Infrastructure owner for core development tools for project planning as well as code review and defect management

KEY SKILLS

👺 Technology strategy

Communication

Project management and Agile
 Mentoring and building technical teams

Systems architecture design and implementation

② EVM and scaling solutions

② Smart contracts in Solidity and Cairo
□ Building REST and GraphQL APIs

High performance low latency development using low-level languages like C++ (17+) and Golang

☑ Building microservice based massively horizontally scalable architectures in Python and Typescript

STRENGTHS

√ Leadership

Mentoring

Curiosity

uperimentation

Rapid Iteration

% Building

EDUCATION

ACHIEVEMENTS

ETH Global Paris

Jul 2023

Hackathon Prize winner :
Best use of Gnosis
Project : Callhook

github.com/konradstrachan/ethparis

ETH Global Prague

Jun 2023

☑ Hackathon Prize winner

Taiko: Infrastructure 1st place

Project : ChainSpecter

ithus are (hamadataahan (athana)

ithus are (hamadataa

github.com/konradstrachan/ethprague

<u>ETHDam Amsterdam</u>

<u>May 2023</u>